A Guide to the Edward Howard House Papers, 1873-1901
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Harper & Bros. to H. re sale Midnight W. 1894 Dec 19, memo, 2 p (Box 5)
- R.H. Lyman to House 1894 Dec 20, TLS, 1 p (Box 5)
- Harper & Brothers to House 1894 Dec 22, ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- R.H. Farrell to House 1894 Dec 26, ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- Henry B. Cosgrove to House 1894 Dec 27, ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- C.C. Buel to House 1895 Jan 10, ALS, 2 p (Box 5)
- F. Brinkley to House [1895 Feb 2], ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- Dr. E. Baelz to House 1895 Feb 17, ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- The World to House 1895 Feb 23, telegram (Box 5)
- R.A. Farrelly to House 1895 Mar 11, TLS, 2 p (Box 5)
- John H. Wigmore to House 1895 Mar 14, ALS, 7 p (Box 5)
- The World to [House] 1895 Mar 15, 2 telegrams (Box 5)
- R.H. Lyman to House 1895 Mar 16, ALS, 4 p (Box 5)
- The World to House 1895 Mar 19, telegram (Box 5)
- R.H. Lyman to House 1895 Apr 2, TLS, 2 p (Box 5)
- The World to House 1895 Apr 5, telegram (Box 5)
- J. Angus Shaw to House 1895 Apr 16, ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- R.H. Lyman to House 1895 Apr 20, TLS, 4 p (Box 5)
- The World to House 1895 Apr 22, telegram (Box 5)
- The World to House 1895 Apr 23, telegram (Box 5)
- J. Angus Shaw to House 1895 Apr 27, ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- The World to House 1895 Apr 30, telegram (Box 5)
- The World to House 1895 May 2, telegram (Box 5)
- The World to House 1895 May 18-1896 Feb 14, 3 cashiers' slips (Box 5)
- R.H. Lyman to House 1895 Jun 1, 2 TLS + account (Box 5)
- The World to House 1895 Jun 2, telegram (Box 5)
- C.C. Buel to House 1895 Jun 5, TLS, 6 p (Box 5)
- R.H. Lyman to House 1895 Jun 7, TLS, 1 p (Box 5)
- to House 1895 Jun 18, cashier's slip (Box 5)
- E. V. Chamberlin to House 1895 Jul 16, TLS, 2 p (Box 5)
- J. Angus Shaw to House 1895 Jul 27, ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- J. Angus Shaw to House 1895 Aug 17, ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- R.H. Lyman to House 1895 Aug 19, TLS, 3 p (Box 5)
- The World to House 1895 Sep 13, TNS (Box 5)
- George W. Bonnell to House 1895 Sep 30, ALS, 4 p (Box 5)
- [Laju?] to Koto House [1895 Nov 10], ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- Sir Ernest Satow to House 1895 Nov 16, ALS, 3 p (Box 5)
- C.C. Buel to House 1895 Nov 29, TLS, 2 p (Box 5)
- Sir Ernest Satow to House 1895 Dec 12, ALS, 2 p (Box 5)
- J. Angus Shaw to House 1895 Dec 16, ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- Sir Ernest Satow to House [1895 Dec 23], ALS, 2 p (Box 5)
- Henry Satoh to House 1896 Feb 1, ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- Sir Ernest Satow to House 1896 Feb 7, ALS, 2 p (Box 5)
- Henry Satoh to House [1896 Feb 13], ALS, 2 p (Box 5)
- R.H. Lyman to House 1896 Feb 26, TLS, 3 p (Box 5)
- Sir Ernest Satow to House [1896 Mar 2], ALS, 2 p (Box 5)
- C.C. Buel to House 1896 Mar 4, TLS, 4 p (Box 5)
- C.C. Buel to House 1896 Mar 10, ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- Helen Elise Villard to Koto House 1896 Apr 15, ALS, 4 p (Box 5)
- Kate B. Barker to Koto House [1896 Apr 19], ALS, 3 p (Box 5)
- Cornelia S.W. Williams to Koto House [1896 Apr], ALS, 2 p (Box 5)
- E.S. Marston to Koto House 1896 May 4, TLS, 1 p (Box 5)
- R.H. Lyman to House 1896 Jul 14, TLS, 1 p (Box 5)
- George Sale to House [1896 Jul 30], ALS, 4 p (Box 5)
- J. Angus Shaw to House 1896 Oct 1, TNS (Box 5)
- George H. Scidmore to House 1897 Jan 5, ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- George H. Scidmore to House 1897 Jan 13, ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- The Shortstory Publishing Co. to House 1897 Jan 27, TL, 1 p (Box 5)
- F. Brinkley to House [1897 Feb 7], ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- J.R. Herod to House [1897 Feb 14], ALS, 3 p (Box 5)
- -- Fox (Harper & Brothers) to House 1897 Feb 16, ANS (Box 5)
- F. Brinkley to House [1897 Mar 26], ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- A. Brisbane to House 1897 Mar 31, TLS, 1 p (Box 5)
- T.D. Lowther to House 1897 May 4, ALS, 4 p (Box 5)
- Harper & Brothers to House 1897 Jun 10, TL, 1 p (Box 5)
- F. Brinkley to House [1898 Jan 20], ALS, 3 p (Box 5)
- Mary Mapes Dodge to House 1898 Apr 29, TLS, 2 p (Box 5)
- A.N. Marquis & Co. to House 1898 May 5, form letter, 1 p (Box 5)
- Eliza C. Scidmore to House [1898 May 18], ALS, 3 p (Box 5)
- The Shortstory Publishing Co. to House 1898 Jun 23, TL, 1 p (Box 5)
- F. Brinkley to House [1898 Jul 18], ALS, 2 p (Box 5)
- editor St. Nicholas Editorial Rooms to H 1898 Aug 11, TLS, 3 p (Box 5)
- F. Brinkley to House [1898] Aug 27, ALS, 2 p (Box 5)
- F. Brinkley to House [1898] Aug 30, ALS, 4 p (Box 5)
- F. Brinkley to House [1898 Sep 5], ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- F. Brinkley to House [1898] Oct 26, ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- George H. Scidmore to House 1898 Dec 23, ALS, 2 p (Box 5)
- Harper & Bros. to House re Midnight W. 1898 Dec 31, memo, 1 p (Box 5)
- W.F. Clarke to House 1899 Jan 17, TLS, 2 p (Box 5)
- Harper & Brothers to House 1899 Mar 28, form letter, 1 p (Box 5)
- John Howard Brown to House 1899 Dec 9, TLS, 1 p (Box 5)
- Harper & Brothers to House 1899 Dec 31, account, 1 p (Box 5)
- F. Brinkley to House [1900 Feb 28], ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- Harper & Brothers to House 1900 Mar 11, TL, 1 p (Box 5)
- Henry Satoh to House 1900 Mar 20, ALS, 2 p (Box 5)
- Marcia A. York to House 1900 Mar 27, ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- Marcia A. York to House [1900 Apr 1], ALS, 2 p (Box 5)
- Marcia A. York to House 1900 Apr 5, ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- Harper & Brothers to House 1900 Apr 30, TN (Box 5)
- Harper & Brothers to House 1900 May 15, TN (Box 5)
- F. Brinkley to House [1900 May 25], ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- Harper & Bros to H 1900 June 30-Dec 31, 2 accounts, 2 form letters, 4 p (Box 5)
- A.N. Marquis & Co. to House 1900 Dec 15, TLS, 1 p (Box 5)
- Henry Satoh to House 1901 Jan 10, ALS, 2 p (Box 5)
- George H. Scidmore to House 1901 Jan 16, ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- James T. White & Co. to House 1901 Jan 24, TLS, 1 p (Box 5)
- F. Brinkley to House [1901 Jan 25], ALS, 2 p (Box 5)
- Harper & Brothers to House 1901 Apr 4, TLS, 2 p (Box 5)
- Rokushiro Uyehara to House 1901 Apr 6, ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- Rokushiro Uyehara to House 1901 Apr 12, ALS, 2 p (Box 5)
- George H. Scidmore to House 1901 Nov 11, ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- George H. Scidmore to House 1901 Nov 20, ALS, 3 p (Box 5)
- --- to Koto House [in Japanese] ---- Apr 23, ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- --- to Koto House [in Japanese] ---- May 9, ALS, 3 p (Box 5)
- --- to Koto House [in Japanese] ---- May 31, ALS, 2 p (Box 5)
- F. Brinkley to House [Thursday] Sep 6, ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- F. Brinkley to House [Monday], ALS, 2 p (Box 5)
- F. Brinkley to Mrs. [Herter?] [Sunday], ALS, 2 p (Box 5)
- C.O. Shepard to House n.d., ALS, 1 p (Box 5)
- --- to Koto House [in Japanese] n.d., AL[S], 1 p (Box 5)
- [guests at premiere?] [House] n.d., list of names, 1 p (Box 5)